What Google
really rewards
Ashley Christian  ·  Groundbreaker Marketing
Google is all
about trust that
is their number
one thing the
reason that they
show you first is
because Google
will trust you
they know that
Google wants to
keep its users on
its platform
that's Google's
entire business
model is keep
people happy keep
their users happy
they do that by
recommending
businesses that
have the highest
likelihood of
treating their
customers well
when they have an
algorithm that
decides who
they're going to
show first
they're looking
for trust your
reviews is a huge
part of that but
another huge part
of that is if
you publish your
prices if you're
up front with
your prices that
is building trust
with Google